<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mohammed Alghazwi Dot Com</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mohammed Alghazwi Dot Com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 18:06:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Pen Testing Experience</title>
      <link>/blog/pent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 18:06:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/pent/</guid>
      <description>When I started, it all seemed so scary and difficult but the more I looked into it the easier it got. For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know penetration testing is the art of finding vulnerabilities in systems, networks, or web applications. Pen testers are among the best in regards to security knowledge and probably the highest paid. During my masters degree, I took a pen testing course and we were instructed to find all vulnerabilities in a given web application and write a report about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>/blog/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 15:16:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/hello/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Blog!
I have been meaning to write a blog for a while now, but I have been too busy. Finally now that I have some spare time to write about what I think on everything. From complicated things like blockchain to simple but awesome things like coffee or travel.
I will also write about what I learn because that can actually help me remember things and help you the reader (hopefully) to understand and do fun things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>{ About }</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Mohammed tries to create things out of software and sometimes he breaks things. He fails often but every once in a while, he stumbles onto something. He loves learning new things and when he is not doing that, he can be seen:  Biking around the city. Hiking in the woods or climbing a mountain. Drinking coffee at the nearest starbucks with his macbook.  { Education }  RMIT University</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>